it's time for Double Double Toil and
Trouble a former intern of Mary Kate and
Ashley olsson's company has filed a
lawsuit against them what claiming she
worked 50h hour weeks under horrible
conditions hey guys cut it out uh the
intern claimed among other things that
she had to go to the hospital for
dehydration after carrying 50 lbs of
trench coats in 100 degree weather like
you do uh and that was just for one of
Mary Kate's summer Friday outfits it it
may not be glamorous slaving for two
pocket witches but at least it goes on
your resume so comedians what are some
terrifying responsibilities you'd list
on your LinkedIn profile from your time
as an olssen intern in 60 seconds and
begin Doug Benson learning to know which
one is Ashley and which one is not
Ashley okay points Michelle find some
old French Dudes that they can marry
point points Doug getting them down when
they get stuck in a tree
points mosha Casher tucking them into
their coffins at
night give them their hourly botox
injection points Mo Casher renewing Dave
kier's restraining order all right
points Doug you have to watch all of
their straight to VHS movies including
Passport to Paris
how do you know what they're called Doug
I don't know
okay good answer Michelle um chew up all
their food and feed it to them um mama
bird style yeah points got to do that
for them Doug 24-hour sagot
[Laughter]
[Applause]
watch